### Sarah Beecroft

Seattle, WA ↑
801-403-4880 
smblair87@gmail.com

Digital Marketer with over 8 years of experience writing engaging copy for B2C campaigns, crafting promotional materials, and fueling positive engagement on social media.

Passionate, hard-working, and looking to grow by breaking into the world of web development. Trained in the MERN stack as of August 2019 and looking for new opportunities, with focus on the front end. Excellent communicator and interested in learning new technologies.

### **Skills and Technologies**

- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, React, Express, and Git
- MySQL and MongoDB
- Project Management
- Atlassian Jira, Trello, Slack, and GitHub Projects

- MailChimp, Office 365, Sprinklr, TweetDeck, Wordpress, and Yesmail
- Content writing for blog posts, social media, and promotional campaigns
- Setting up and monitoring marketing email campaigns from start to finish

### **Experience**

DATES: MAY 2016 - PRESENT

# JeffreyM Consulting (Microsoft) - Bellevue, WA Xbox Community Manager

- Monitors all inbound content on Xbox social media channels including: Twitter, Facebook, Instagram, and YouTube
- Reactively engages with fans, prospects, and customers on official Xbox channels
- Assists with customer support and technical inquiries
- Discovers trending topics, themes, and consumer interests and needs across social media
- Creates and distributes weekly/monthly reports on social activity
- Brainstorms campaign and proactive post ideas with Xbox marketing team based on trends

#### **Social Listening Manager**

- Managed social listening team of 6 for Microsoft project
- Compiled keyword lists and scanned social media for keywords
- Put together reports on trends/themes based on keyword listening
- Managerial duties such as: team scheduling, weekly 1:1s, and performance reviews
- Tested key product features for quality assurance

#### **Retail Community Manager**

- Improved customer satisfaction and built customer insights by monitoring Surface and PC Accessory product reviews at online retailers, primarily Amazon
- Crafted individual responses to consumers and prospects regarding Surface and PC Accessory devices
- Provided answers to Surface and PC Accessory product questions online
- Managed multiple email aliases and responded directly to email inquiries regarding support and product questions

DATES: SEPTEMBER 2014 - MAY 2016

## TaskEasy - Salt Lake City, UT Email & Content Manager

- Wrote, designed, and monitored all company marketing and informational email campaigns
- Redesigned and updated all company transactional emails (order confirmation, order updates, etc.)
- Wrote fun and informative content for website and company blog
- Brainstormed ideas with the team for email campaigns, promotions, and sales
- Set up logistics behind contests and promotions
- Monitored and responded to customer reviews via ShopperApproved
- Set up and monitored all paid social media campaigns on Twitter and Facebook
- Engaged with customers and prospects on Twitter and Facebook

#### **Education**

DATES: FEBRUARY 2019 - AUGUST 2019

## **University of Washington Coding Boot Camp Part-Time Full Stack Program**

- Certificate Program
- MERN stack specialization
  - o MongoDB, Express, React, and Node.js

#### **Activities**

- Won Employee of the Month at both JeffreyM Consulting and TaskEasy
- Completed HTML/CSS/JavaScript courses with Codecademy
- Participated in Ragnar Relay Wasatch Back with team of 11 coworkers